Azim Akmatov

+996 500 512 611 · azim.akmatov1@gmail.com · akmatoff.com · linkedin.com/in/akmatoff

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Front-end developer with 2 years commercial experience. Worked with partners like Binance, Gcash, Vodapay, Touch'N'Go using technologies like Alipay's Mini Program Development Platform and Angular. Contributed to e-commerce platform Shopboxo using React and Next.js. Created and still working on side project <u>codiumdev.com</u> using NestJS, React and Next.js.

SKILLS

Programming: TypeScript - React - Next.js - Angular - Vite - Tanstack Query - Redux Toolkit - Playwright - TailwindCSS - Sass - NextUI - Framer Motion - React-Hook-Form - AJAX - Node.js - PostgreSQL

Other: Foundational understanding of UI/UX - Responsive Design - Team Collaboration - Attention to details - Docker - Linode (VPS) - Basic nginx - Vercel - Github Actions

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Appboxo

Front-End Developer Intern

February 2022 - May 2022

- Troubleshooted and resolved issues reported by support team within 48 hours, resolving 4+ issues a
 day.
- Assisted team in fixing over 50 bugs which increased feature delivery speed.
- Ensured miniapps stability and functionality by resolving issues and implementing requested customizations.
- Participated in team meetings and discussions to grow knowledge.
- Communicated with partners and clients to better understand the issues and resolve them.
- Supported 3+ projects including web-based miniapps, non-web miniapps and Shopboxo seller-side dashboard, using Angular, Alipay's Miniapp Framework and React.

Appboxo

Junior Front-End Developer

June 2022 - February 2024

- Developed and deployed 10+ new features and customizations for miniapps using Angular and Alipay's Mini Program Framework.
- Supported 5+ major partners including Binance, Gcash, Touch'N'Go, Vodapay, PayTM, Unacash by resolving issues and delivering new features and customizations.
- Covered platform with E2E testing with Playwright, enhancing platform stability.
- Delivered 5+ new major features for e-commerce platform which include product modifiers, discounts, cross-selling, a product description editor, an order timeline and others using React and Next.js.
- Refactored around 20% of the codebase, improving performance.
- Collaborated with partners and clients to resolve issues, achieving a client satisfaction rate of around 90%.

EDUCATION

IUCA College

Information Technologies (2018-2021) Associate's Degree

PROJECTS

codiumdev.com

A platform for organization which provides programming courses which includes the admin panel, the landing page and the platform for students to make studying and management easier.